

WENDEL AMANTE

SUMMARY

Creative Digital Marketer and Graphic Designer with 4 years of solid experience in broad range of industries. Well- trained at visual strategy, layout development, branding, and new media advertising. Demonstrated success working in collaborative environment, manifest leadership to execute effective marketing collateral.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Graphic Designing Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Canva
Marketing & Social Media Management MailChimp, ClickUp, Zoho
Microsoft Office 365 Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint
Content Management System & Database WordPress, Wix, Magento, Shopify, MySQL
Web Developing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Php, Codelgniter, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Github

EXPERIENCES

Graphics Assistant (Freelance)

Nov 2023 - Dec 2024 Intralux Australia

Led the brochure revamp, modernizing design and branding. Produced high-quality vector drawings based on provided instructions. Assisted the marketing team with various promotional materials.

Mapping Specialist (Freelance)

Jan 2024 - Feb 2024 SPS Training & Consultancy Services, Inc.

Contributed to the successful debut of Promil's The Gifted Brain Room Project. Managed email communications and conducted cold calls to stakeholders. Updated database through research and data gathering.

Digital Marketing Associate (Project- based)

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023 IMPACT Training and Consultancy Services

Collaborated with brands for online promotions.

Created engaging content and scheduled posts.

Engaged with online communities and responded to inquiries.

Digital Marketer w/ Graphic Design

Oct 2022 - Aug 2023 Beepo Inc. | IS Apparel Pty Ltd Australia

Designed and led digital marketing, including email and display ads. Planned and managed social media platforms.

Developed and optimized Meta Ads for Facebook and Instagram.

• Freelance Graphic Designer

Aug 2021 - Aug 2022

Created mockups, logos, banners, and posters.

Made PowerPoint presentations and documentation.

Contributed to web design using WordPress, Wix, Magento, and Shopify.

Web Developer & Graphic Designer Intern

Feb 2022 - May 2022 Inner SPARC Realty Services

Produced content for websites, presentations, social media, and marketing. Developed websites using WordPress.

• Lead Graphic Designer/ Social Media Manager/ Web Designer and Developer

June 2020 - June 2021

Street Mavens Clothing Company

Designed logos and graphics for a streetwear brand. Supervised the graphic design team. Maintained a consistent social media feed through content creation

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Cavite State University - Imus Campus President's Lister

CERTIFICATIONS

SMART Android Mobile App Development TESDA Online Program | 2022
Fortinet's Network Security Expert Certification NSE 1 and NSE 2 Fortinet | 2020
TESDA 2D Animation NC II Genesis Innovations and Creative Design Training Center Inc. | 2018